Marek Sadura

Senior Full Stack Javascript Engineer Lublin, Poland (GMT +2) linkedin.com/in/marek-sadura-epicode github.com/msadura marek@epicode.solutions +48 693737572 I am a versatile Software Engineer with 10 years of professional experience in both frontend and back-end technologies. My aim is to develop software with the best possible quality, accessible UI, made user-first. Possessing the skill sets to effectively step-up as a leader and mentor, while remaining a strong individual contributor. Very enthusiastic about blockchain and web3 development.

Skills -

Javascript | Typescript | React | React Native | Node.js | Next.js | Styled Components | Tailwind CSS |
Web3 | Ethersjs | Prisma | PostgreSQL | Solidity | AWS | Jest | Playwright | Serverless

Work Experience ————

Senior Full Stack Engineer

THORSwap Finance

Jan 2022 - Current

- Implementing redesigned Decentralized Crypto Exchange interface using React, Redux, tailwindcss. Creating and delivering solution for Thorchain multisig wallet.
- Creating design system based on atomic components and storybook, considering mobile devices.
- Actively improving UI and UX, based on experience refactoring existing logic to achieve long-term sustainability.
- Integrating interface with THORChain api, providing announcements Node.js service.

Main technologies: Typescript, React, Ethersjs, Tailwind CSS, Redux, Redux-toolkit, Node.js

Senior Javascript Developer Slin

Sling scheduling

Feb 2017 - Jun 2022

Building in-house platform for employee scheduling

- Implementing and supporting AngularJS core web app, testing app logic in mocha.
- Introducing React to the project, rewriting web app to React. Designing react app architecture to follow modern code standards.
- Leading on mobile app development in React Native for iOS and android devices. Building CI pipeline for releases using fastlane.
- Working on improving product UI and UX, using best code practises and building base components based on design system.

Main technologies: Javascript, Typescript, React, React Native, Redux, Rxjs, Styled Components, Storybook, Jest, Mocha

Senior Software Developer

BLStream (rebranded to Intive)

Mar 2014 - Feb 2017

- Building the official Oscars website in AngularJS https://oscars.go.com/
- Implementing RWD interfaces, working on large variety of devices satisfying customer needs.
- Implementing SEO friendly AngularJS app with pre-rendering content on the server.
- Working close to the customer, gathering requirements and implementing functionalities under the pressure of time.
- Mentoring junior developers.

Main technologies: Javascript, Typescript, Angular JS, React, Mocha, Less, Redux, AWS

Software Developer

Select Sp. Z o.o.

Jun 2011 - Mar 2014

- Customizing ZenCart based ecommerce platforms.
- Supporting and expanding functionalities of CRM systems based on SugarCRM, introducing AngularJS to the project.
- Implementing designs and RWD interfaces.

Main technologies: PHP, MySQL, Javascript, CSSs, AngularJS, nginx

Projects -

Memes Art Aug 2021 - Jun 2022

https://memes.art - web3 app that allows user to create a meme and generate it onchain as NFT. Own project used to learn Solidity basics. Built with React and Next.is, Solidity and hardhat.

Education -